{
  "addition": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "problem": "$1 + 10$",
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "problem": "$12 + 4$",
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "problem": "$1 + 8$",
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "problem": "$8 + 3$",
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "problem": "$16 + 10$",
      "answer": 26
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "problem": "$15 + 9$",
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "problem": "$8 + 10$",
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "problem": "$13 + 9$",
      "answer": 22
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "problem": "$20 + 15$",
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "problem": "$20 + 10$",
      "answer": 30
    }
  ]
}